UX Designer

Zoe Ellen Pointon

London UK 07935 408 399 zoepointon123@gmail.com zoeellenpointon.com UX designer with a passion for creating user centred products, based research and data. 3 years experience working within the tech industry as a designer. Masters in Design Informatics from the University of Edinburgh.

Skills

Adobe CC Sketch Invision Google Analytics Adobe Analytics HTML CSS Python

Certifications

Google

The Online Marketing Fundamentals

Awards

University of Edinburgh

Oberlander Prize Design Informatics MA

University of Winchester

Transmedia 2017 Pitch a Project Winner

References

Sky

Jennifer Hards

TBC

TruDigital

Allan Crabtree

allan@allancrabtree.co.uk

CDG

Sally Hanson

sally@shml.co.uk

Experience

December 2019 - Present

Junior UX Designer - Sky

Maintaining service journeys on the OTT platform (NOW TV).

August 2018 - November 2019 (1 year 4 months)

UX Consultant - Maxivation

Freelance work alone side my masters.

April 2018 - August 2018 (5 months)

UX Designer - TruDigital

Formerly part of CDG. Working in a start-up environment allowed me to take more ownership of existing client projects. Creating actionable conversion reports became the greatest part of my role.

May 2017 - April 2018 (1 year)

Graduate Designer - CDG

After graduating I joined CDG full-time. I worked on client projects; designing eCommerce and booking sites. At CDG I also got the opportunity to work on internal projects working as part of a small agile products team to deliver B to C mobile applications.

May 2016 - April 2017 (1 year)

Digital Design Intern - CDG

During my last year at university I got the opportunity to work alongside my degree as a design intern.

Education

2018 - 2019

University of Edinburgh - MA Design Informatics

Grade: Distinction

2014 - 2017

University of Winchester - BA Digital Media Design

Grade: First